(window.webpackJsonp=window.webpackJsonp||[]).push([[0],[,,function(e){e.exports=[{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20hero%20in%20the%2080s%20animated%20video%20game%20%27Dragon%27s%20Lair%27%3F",correct_answer:"Dirk%20the%20Daring",incorrect_answers:["Arthur","Sir%20Toby%20Belch","Guy%20of%20Gisbourne"]},{category:"Animals",type:"multiple",difficulty:"easy",question:"What%20is%20the%20scientific%20name%20for%20modern%20day%20humans%3F",correct_answer:"Homo%20Sapiens",incorrect_answers:["Homo%20Ergaster","Homo%20Erectus","Homo%20Neanderthalensis"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Books",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"What%20is%20Ron%20Weasley%27s%20middle%20name%3F",correct_answer:"Bilius",incorrect_answers:["Arthur","John","Dominic"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Comics",type:"multiple",difficulty:"easy",question:"Who%20is%20the%20creator%20of%20the%20comic%20series%20%22The%20Walking%20Dead%22%3F",correct_answer:"Robert%20Kirkman",incorrect_answers:["Stan%20Lee","Malcolm%20Wheeler-Nicholson","Robert%20Crumb"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Board%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"At%20the%20start%20of%20a%20standard%20game%20of%20the%20Monopoly%2C%20if%20you%20throw%20a%20double%20six%2C%20which%20square%20would%20you%20land%20on%3F",correct_answer:"Electric%20Company",incorrect_answers:["Water%20Works","Chance","Community%20Chest"]},{category:"Geography",type:"multiple",difficulty:"easy",question:"What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Jamaica%3F",correct_answer:"Kingston",incorrect_answers:["Rio%20de%20Janeiro","Dar%20es%20Salaam","Kano"]},{category:"History",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"When%20did%20Jamaica%20recieve%20its%20independence%20from%20England%3F%20",correct_answer:"1962",incorrect_answers:["1492","1963","1987"]},{category:"Animals",type:"boolean",difficulty:"easy",question:"Kangaroos%20keep%20food%20in%20their%20pouches%20next%20to%20their%20children.",correct_answer:"False",incorrect_answers:["True"]},{category:"General%20Knowledge",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"In%202013%20how%20much%20money%20was%20lost%20by%20Nigerian%20scams%3F",correct_answer:"%2412.7%20Billion",incorrect_answers:["%2495%20Million","%24956%20Million","%242.7%20Billion"]},{category:"History",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"How%20old%20was%20Lyndon%20B.%20Johnson%20when%20he%20assumed%20the%20role%20of%20President%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F",correct_answer:"55",incorrect_answers:["50","60","54"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"In%20World%20of%20Warcraft%20lore%2C%20who%20organized%20the%20creation%20of%20the%20Paladins%3F",correct_answer:"Alonsus%20Faol",incorrect_answers:["Uther%20the%20Lightbringer","Alexandros%20Mograine","Sargeras%2C%20The%20Daemon%20Lord"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"boolean",difficulty:"medium",question:"In%20the%20game%20%22Subnautica%22%2C%20a%20%22Cave%20Crawler%22%20will%20attack%20you.",correct_answer:"True",incorrect_answers:["False"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20device%20that%20allows%20for%20infinite%20energy%20in%20the%20anime%20%22Dimension%20W%22%3F",correct_answer:"Coils",incorrect_answers:["Wires","Collectors","Tesla"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20Cream%20the%20Rabbit%27s%20mom%20in%20the%20%22Sonic%20the%20Hedgehog%22%20series%3F",correct_answer:"Vanilla",incorrect_answers:["Peach","Strawberry","Mint"]},{category:"History",type:"multiple",difficulty:"easy",question:"These%20two%20countries%20held%20a%20commonwealth%20from%20the%2016th%20to%2018th%20century.",correct_answer:"Poland%20and%20Lithuania",incorrect_answers:["Hutu%20and%20Rwanda","North%20Korea%20and%20South%20Korea","Bangladesh%20and%20Bhutan"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Television",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"Which%20of%20these%20voices%20wasn%27t%20a%20choice%20for%20the%20House%20AI%20in%20%22The%20Simpsons%20Treehouse%20of%20Horror%22%20short%2C%20House%20of%20Whacks%3F",correct_answer:"George%20Clooney",incorrect_answers:["Matthew%20Perry","Dennis%20Miller","Pierce%20Brosnan"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Music",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"From%20which%20album%20is%20the%20Gorillaz%20song%2C%20%22On%20Melancholy%20Hill%22%20featured%20in%3F",correct_answer:"Plastic%20Beach",incorrect_answers:["Demon%20Days","Humanz","The%20Fall"]},{category:"General%20Knowledge",type:"boolean",difficulty:"easy",question:"Scotland%20voted%20to%20become%20an%20independent%20country%20during%20the%20referendum%20from%20September%202014.",correct_answer:"False",incorrect_answers:["True"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"In%20Left%204%20Dead%2C%20which%20campaign%20has%20the%20protagonists%20going%20through%20a%20subway%20in%20order%20to%20reach%20a%20hospital%20for%20evacuation%3F",correct_answer:"No%20Mercy",incorrect_answers:["Subway%20Sprint","Hospital%20Havoc","Blood%20Harvest"]},{category:"History",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"What%20was%20the%20last%20colony%20the%20UK%20ceded%20marking%20the%20end%20of%20the%20British%20Empire%3F",correct_answer:"Hong%20Kong",incorrect_answers:["India","Australia","Ireland"]}]},function(e,t){e.exports="data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAADAAAAAwCAYAAABXAvmHAAAABmJLR0QA/wD/AP+gvaeTAAABy0lEQVRoge2YS0vDQBSFvwruBB/gE4TahS22KPjbBHfq0pXiRnFhXQu61J/hzvqguu6i0FYpYqmPRaYYa5LOTDOZRHPgQgi5Z865Z6akgRQpUqTwwRJQAW6BnGUtWrgAPkWdW9aijBLwzreBD2DNqiJFuKefuBT6p5+4FLymn5gU/KafmBSCph/7FAZNP/YpyEw/tinITj/0FDIaPXNAAVgG8uJ6XdxXQQ24Bu6Ae+BBXNdUSPwMjAKLQBFYwXmXyQGrwIyiUFW0gCrwJKoC3OCYa8sQbAFvyG+HqKojtP2AVwINYELGqQU0gUn3jRGPh06j0aKFssxDGeAI+1umv8p4DzwRJpTEx82Elni3iUOL4k+GEW/bRCjibZkIVXzUJoyIj8qEUfE9lAwaKKqK0XGb1+gxxq1joKDRY4z7XyYQKwM6aGDuEDdNi583KL5XSn9NVbdQFBErrWHSQB3YEFVX6DP5K8c+g7fAC7ALjLv6xoBN5M7PnkkDVwELt4EDYDagfwrYAZ4DeC4NaQfg0WPBDnAMLCjwTOOk9OrBVw1R7y+4J9fF+QCQHYIvKzi6Lt7WkBoDsY1zIM8I97AVBGcdj28/KVKk+MP4AvA0BCbb6Y+iAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC"},function(e,t){e.exports="data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABgAAAAYCAYAAADgdz34AAAABmJLR0QA/wD/AP+gvaeTAAABMUlEQVRIidXUTUsDMRAG4Kda/KiK1u9C/QUe1JtHf7onQRBvHlQQsaWlJxEUioL1kG1dlmy7q3vpC4FkMvO+SWYyzDtqJXzXcJHML/FRJGixhMA59rCMBl6KBC0UJN9GO7U+wm6VAqcR20lVAoc4iNj3k72pmJaDhvAMZ1jJ8WkKyf7GV8whXUVttLCZjKVZp8vgE2/J6KObFmj5LcGqcIn+OAejisknnOMcvCfzvYrI7/GYFoCBkMydf5I/4Ha8yFZRD6vCx/oLnnCTNsTKtI8NbJUkf8a1TD5jH22kYJ/JoJMlzxMg3KAs1mPGPIGo8wxED1XlDUoJ5N2gl4zCMfUc53RzGwl95Q6via2JY6F/1SIxE+R107rQ8Lq4En7lMLU/FCqtIzTFRuIzyOGbY/wAzlguxTUBcZcAAAAASUVORK5CYII="},,,function(e,t,a){e.exports=a(15)},,,,,,function(e,t,a){},function(e,t,a){},function(e,t,a){"use strict";a.r(t);var n=a(0),r=a.n(n),o=a(6),i=a.n(o),c=(a(13),a(1)),s=(a(14),a(2)),l=a(3),m=a.n(l),u=a(4),d=a.n(u);var h=function(){var e=r.a.useState(0),t=Object(c.a)(e,2),a=t[0],o=t[1],i=r.a.useState(1),l=Object(c.a)(i,2),u=l[0],h=l[1],y=r.a.useState(0),g=Object(c.a)(y,2),w=g[0],A=g[1],f=r.a.useState(0),p=Object(c.a)(f,2),E=p[0],b=p[1],C=r.a.useState([]),v=Object(c.a)(C,2),B=v[0],F=v[1],S=r.a.useState([]),_=Object(c.a)(S,2),D=_[0],q=_[1],K=r.a.useState([]),G=Object(c.a)(K,2),k=G[0],O=G[1],j=r.a.useState(!0),M=Object(c.a)(j,2),W=M[0],J=M[1],H=r.a.useState(0),Q=Object(c.a)(H,2),R=Q[0],U=Q[1],I=r.a.useState(0),N=Object(c.a)(I,2),T=N[0],L=N[1],Y=r.a.useState(0),V=Object(c.a)(Y,2),x=V[0],P=V[1],z=r.a.useState(0),X=Object(c.a)(z,2),Z=X[0],$=X[1],ee=r.a.useState([]),te=Object(c.a)(ee,2),ae=te[0],ne=te[1],re=function(e){e.target.innerText===s[E].correct_answer.replace(/%3A%20|%20/g," ").replace(/%27|%3F|%22|%2C/g,"")?(O("Correct!"),U(R+1)):(O("Sorry!"),L(T+1));for(var t=document.getElementsByClassName("answers"),a=0;a<t.length;a++)t[a].disabled=!0;J(!1)};return Object(n.useEffect)(function(){switch(o(s.length),A(100*u/a),s[E].difficulty){case"easy":F(r.a.createElement(r.a.Fragment,null,r.a.createElement("img",{src:m.a,alt:""}),r.a.createElement("img",{src:d.a,alt:""}),r.a.createElement("img",{src:d.a,alt:""})));break;case"medium":F(r.a.createElement(r.a.Fragment,null,r.a.createElement("img",{src:m.a,alt:""}),r.a.createElement("img",{src:m.a,alt:""}),r.a.createElement("img",{src:d.a,alt:""})));break;case"hard":F(r.a.createElement(r.a.Fragment,null,r.a.createElement("img",{src:m.a,alt:""}),r.a.createElement("img",{src:m.a,alt:""}),r.a.createElement("img",{src:m.a,alt:""})))}P(100*R/a),$(100-100*T/a)},[w,W]),Object(n.useEffect)(function(){var e=[r.a.createElement("button",{className:"answers",onClick:re},s[E].correct_answer.replace(/%3A%20|%20/g," ").replace(/%27|%3F|%22|%2C|%24/g,""))];s[E].incorrect_answers.map(function(t,a,n){e.push(r.a.createElement("button",{className:"answers",onClick:re},t.replace(/%3A%20|%20/g," ").replace(/%27|%3F|%22|%2C|%24/g,"")))}),ne(e)},[ae]),Object(n.useMemo)(function(){console.log(ae),function(e){for(var t=e.length-1;t>0;t--){var a=Math.floor(Math.random()*(t+1)),n=e[t];e[t]=e[a],e[a]=n}}(ae),q(ae)},[w]),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"App"},r.a.createElement("div",{id:"progressBar",style:{width:"".concat(w,"%")}}),r.a.createElement("div",{id:"bigOverlay"},r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement("h1",null," Question ",u," of ",a," "),r.a.createElement("h3",null,s[E].category.replace(/%3A/g,":").replace(/%20/g," ")),r.a.createElement("div",{id:"starOverlay"},r.a.createElement("small",{className:"stars"}," ",B," "))),r.a.createElement("p",{className:"question"},s[E].question.replace(/%3A%20|%20/g," ").replace(/%27|%3F|%22|%2C/g,"")),r.a.createElement("div",{id:"answers"},D),r.a.createElement("h2",{id:"answerStatus"},k),r.a.createElement("button",{id:"nextQuestion",onClick:function(){u<a&&(h(u+1),b(E+1));for(var e=document.getElementsByClassName("answers"),t=0;t<e.length;t++)e[t].disabled=!1;J(!0),O("")},disabled:W},"Next Question"),r.a.createElement("div",{id:"scoreChat"},r.a.createElement("span",null,x,"%")," ",r.a.createElement("span",null,Z,"%"),r.a.createElement("div",{id:"scoreOverlay"},r.a.createElement("div",{id:"maxScore",style:{width:"".concat(Z,"%")}},r.a.createElement("div",{id:"score",style:{width:"".concat(x,"%")}}))))))};Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));i.a.render(r.a.createElement(h,null),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then(function(e){e.unregister()})}],[[7,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.8e4cbf9a.chunk.js.map